Welcome to Same's Virtual Tech Garage!
Добро пожаловать в Виртуальный Техно-Гараж Самэ!
This is where we explore the "why?" hidden in everyday life
Здесь мы исследуем скрытые «почему?» повседневной жизни
A secret base that unravels mysteries through VR and science
Секретная база, где разгадывают тайны с помощью VR и науки
We cover physics, computer science, and the history of science
Мы изучаем физику, информатику и историю науки
From the rainbow colors of soap bubbles to atoms, earthquakes, and gravity
От радужных переливов мыльных пузырей к атомам, землетрясениям и гравитации
Tracing messages from supernova explosions preserved in the deep sea
Прослеживаем послания сверхновых, сохранившиеся в глубинах океана
Sorting algorithms that reveal the depth of arranging numbers
Алгоритмы сортировки, раскрывающие глубину упорядочивания чисел
To untold stories of great scientists
И малоизвестные истории великих учёных
For those who want to see the familiar world from a different angle
Для тех, кто хочет взглянуть на знакомый мир под другим углом
From everyday wonders to cosmic mysteries
От повседневных чудес до тайн космоса
Won't you explore the fascination of science and technology with us?
Давайте вместе исследовать увлекательный мир науки и технологий!